<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Health Monitor</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Questions</string>

    <string name="main_header">How healthy are you?</string>
    <string name="main_body">Take this test and see if you need to get some routine medical tests.</string>
    <string name="take_test">Take the test</string>
    <string name="main_image_description">3 people, each holding a big puzzle piece</string>

    <string name="your_bmi">Your health and your body weight are highly related. Your BMI is %1$.2f.</string>

    <string name="diabetes">Diabetes</string>
    <string-array name="diabetes_test_names">
        <item>Fasting blood sugar test</item>
        <item>Glycated hemoglobin test</item>
        <item>Oral glucose tolerance test</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="diabetes_test_descriptions">
        <item>A blood sample will be taken after an overnight fast.\nA fasting blood sugar level less than 100 mg/dL (5.6 mmol/L) is normal.\nA fasting blood sugar level from 100 to 125 mg/dL (5.6 to 6.9 mmol/L) is considered prediabetes.\nIf it\'s 126 mg/dL (7 mmol/L) or higher on two separate tests, you have diabetes.</item>
        <item>This blood test, which doesn\'t require fasting, indicates your average blood sugar level for the past two to three months.\nIt measures the percentage of blood sugar attached to hemoglobin, the oxygen-carrying protein in red blood cells.</item>
        <item>	For this test, you fast overnight, and the fasting blood sugar level is measured.\nThen you drink a sugary liquid, and blood sugar levels are tested periodically for the next two hours.\nA blood sugar level less than 140 mg/dL (7.8 mmol/L) is normal.\nA reading of more than 200 mg/dL (11.1 mmol/L) after two hours indicates diabetes.\nA reading between 140 and 199 mg/dL (7.8 mmol/L and 11.0 mmol/L) indicates prediabetes.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="cardio">Cardiovascular disease</string>
    <string-array name="cardio_test_names">
        <item>Electrocardiogram (ECG or EKG)</item>
        <item>Holter monitoring</item>
        <item>Echocardiogram</item>
        <item>Stress test</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cardio_test_descriptions">
        <item>	An ECG is a quick and painless test that records the electrical signals in your heart.\nIt can spot abnormal heart rhythms. You may have an ECG while you\'re at rest or while exercising (stress electrocardiogram).</item>
        <item>A Holter monitor is a portable ECG device you wear to continuously record your heart rhythm, usually for 24 to 72 hours.\nHolter monitoring is used to detect heart rhythm problems that aren\'t found during a regular ECG exam.</item>
        <item>This noninvasive exam uses sound waves to produce detailed images of your heart\'s structure.\nIt shows how your heart beats and pumps blood.</item>
        <item>This type of test involves raising your heart rate with exercise or medicine while performing heart tests and imaging to check how your heart responds.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="liver">Liver disease</string>
    <string-array name="liver_test_names">
        <item>Alanine transaminase (ALT)</item>
        <item>Aspartate transaminase (AST)</item>
        <item>Alkaline phosphatase (ALP)</item>
        <item>Albumin and total protein</item>
        <item>Bilirubin</item>
        <item>Gamma-glutamyltransferase (GGT)</item>
        <item>L-lactate dehydrogenase (LD)</item>
        <item>Prothrombin time (PT)</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="liver_test_descriptions">
        <item>ALT is an enzyme found in the liver that helps convert proteins into energy for the liver cells. When the liver is damaged, ALT is released into the bloodstream and levels increase.</item>
        <item>AST is an enzyme that helps metabolize amino acids. Like ALT, AST is normally present in blood at low levels. An increase in AST levels may indicate liver damage, disease or muscle damage.</item>
        <item>ALP is an enzyme found in the liver and bone and is important for breaking down proteins. Higher-than-normal levels of ALP may indicate liver damage or disease, such as a blocked bile duct, or certain bone diseases.</item>
        <item>Albumin is one of several proteins made in the liver. Your body needs these proteins to fight infections and to perform other functions. Lower-than-normal levels of albumin and total protein may indicate liver damage or disease.</item>
        <item>Bilirubin is a substance produced during the normal breakdown of red blood cells.\nBilirubin passes through the liver and is excreted in stool.\nElevated levels of bilirubin (jaundice) might indicate liver damage or disease or certain types of anemia.</item>
        <item>GGT is an enzyme in the blood. Higher-than-normal levels may indicate liver or bile duct damage.</item>
        <item>LD is an enzyme found in the liver. Elevated levels may indicate liver damage but can be elevated in many other disorders.</item>
        <item>PT is the time it takes your blood to clot.\nIncreased PT may indicate liver damage but can also be elevated if you\'re taking certain blood-thinning drugs, such as warfarin.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="kidney">Kidney disease</string>
    <string-array name="kidney_test_names">
        <item>Blood tests</item>
        <item>Urine tests</item>
        <item>Imaging tests</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="kidney_test_descriptions">
        <item>Kidney function tests look for the level of waste products, such as creatinine and urea, in your blood.</item>
        <item>Analyzing a sample of your urine may reveal abnormalities that point to chronic kidney failure and help identify the cause of chronic kidney disease.</item>
        <item>Your doctor may use ultrasound to assess your kidneys structure and size. Other imaging tests may be used in some cases.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
